Alvin Goosby Jr.

Cargo Van and Box truck driver with 10+ years of experience

Red Oak, TX 75154 alvingoosbyjr5_j9t@indeedemail.com +1 318 820 5481

To obtain a warehouse manager position with an established logistics company that allows me to use a combination of 6 years of experience in warehouse operations, driving and educational background.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Independent Contractor Driver

Excel Delivery Systems - Dallas, TX April 2021 to Present

Delivered packages promptly and accurately while using the safest and most efficient delivery routes. Loaded and unloaded packages from a 16 foot truck. Completed and submitted all necessary logs and paperwork on a daily basis. Fostered positive working relationships with customers by responding to their questions and concerns. Obeyed traffic laws and followed established traffic and transportation procedures. Inspected truck and truck equipment in order to ensure that vehicle was in proper working condition. Attended and participated in training to remain aware of current trends, advancements, best practices in safe driving, and the safe handling of heavy loads.

Driver (Over Night Shift)

American Tire Distributors - Carrollton, TX June 2014 to April 2021

Loading and unloading the truck in preparations for round trip, transportation of tires, rims, and hydraulic jacks from ATD's Carrollton Texas branch to the Oklahoma City Oklahoma branch. Confirming the product in the truck matches the delivery packing slip. In addition to operating forklifts. Keeping up with bi-annual physical exams to maintain my position as a driver per ATD standards.

Delivery Driver/Warehouseman

Tire Dealer Warehouse - Irving, TX June 2012 to June 2014

Worked for TDW until they were bought out by American Tire Distributors in June 2014. Loading, unloading, operating forklifts and pickers. Stocking tires and pulling orders for customers. Completing a physical exam to gain experience working as a Delivery Driver. Ensuring tires are delivered in a timely manner, at various customer locations in the Dallas/Fort Worth metroplex.

Delivery Driver

Morrison and Dickson Company - Shreveport, LA September 2011 to March 2012

Worked for TDW until they were bought out by American Tire Distributors in June 2014. Loading, unloading, operating forklifts and pickers. Stocking tires and pulling orders for customer. Completing a

physical exam to gain experience working as a Delivery Driver. Ensuring tires are delivered in a timely manner, at varies customer locations in the Dallas/Fort Worth metroplex.

Morrison and Dickson Company, Shreveport, LA Sept 2011 - March 2012

Warehouse Worker (Temp)

Organizing, labeling and wrapping packages to designated per department standards. Creating an organized pallet for forklifts to retrieve and load to the truck for shipment.

Supervisor Driver

Alvin's Delivery & Moving Service - Shreveport, LA July 2009 to September 2011

Working the family business in a supervisory role, receiving calls from clients, entering orders into the system and quoting prices on varies delivery services. Scheduling eMoves to clients that requested services via U-Haul recommendation website. In addition to training employees on loading, unloading and delivering product in a timely manner.

Supervisor Driver

Tommy's Delivery & Moving Service - Shreveport, LA April 2006 to July 2009

Working in a supervisory role, training employees to providing great customer service to clients. Delivering furniture to clients in a timely manner, by safely loading, unloading and delivering to shipping manifest.

Education

Associate of Science in Business Office Management

Remington College - Shreveport, LA July 2009 to July 2011

Skills

- Forklifts
- · Pickers
- · Box Truck Driver
- Inventory Scanners
- Team Management
- Microsoft Office Suites